A Guide to the China Medical Board, Inc. records, RG 1 FA065
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Peking Union Medical College Reports, 1933 (Box P 6, Folder 108)
- Peking Union Medical College Reports, 1934 (Box P 6, Folder 109)
- Peking Union Medical College Reports, 1935 (Box P 6, Folder 110)
- Peking Union Medical College Reports, 1936 (Box P 6, Folder 111)
- Peking Union Medical College Reports, 1937 (Box P 6, Folder 112)
- Peking Union Medical College Reports, 1938 (Box P 6, Folder 113)
- Peking Union Medical College Reports, 1939 (Box P 6, Folder 114)
- Peking Union Medical College Reports, 1940 (Box P 6, Folder 115)
- Peking Union Medical College School of Nursing Announcements, 1927-1930 (Box P 6, Folder 116)
- Peking Union Medical College School of Nursing Announcements, 1930-1933 (Box P 6, Folder 117)
- Peking Union Medical College School of Nursing Announcements, 1933-1936 (Box P 6, Folder 118)
- Peking Union Medical College School of Nursing Announcements, 1936-1938 (Box P 6, Folder 119)
- Peking Union Medical College School of Nursing Announcements, 1938-1940 (Box P 6, Folder 120)
- Peking Union Medical College School of Nursing Announcements, 1940-1941; Copy 1 (Box P 6, Folder 121)
- Peking Union Medical College School of Nursing Announcements, 1940-1941; Copy 2 (Box P 6, Folder 122)
- Peking Union Medical College Announcement, 1921-1922 (Box P 6, Folder 123)
- Peking Union Medical College Announcement, 1922-1923 (Box P 6, Folder 124)
- Peking Union Medical College Announcement, 1925-1926 (Box P 6, Folder 125)
- China Medical Board, Inc. History and Program - Financial Report, 1950-1951 (Box P 6, Folder 126)
- China Medical Board of New York, Inc. Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box P 6, Folder 127)
- Biennial Report 2008-2010 (Box 197)
- Biennial Report 2010-2012 (Box 197)
- Report 2005-2006 (Box 197)
- China Medical Board Medical Education Workshop, 2008 (Box 197)
- Peking Union Medical College - Minutes, 1916-1941 (Box 198)
- Peking Union Medical College - Minutes, 1943-1950 (Box 199)
- Peking Union Medical College - Post-War Inventory, 1947 (Box 199)
- China Medical Board, Inc. photographs, 1918-1950; 1048
  Photographs
  - Miscellaneous/Unknown, 1 (Box 25, Folder 301)
    - Columns of an ancient ruin, undated
    - Crowd gathered at Chinese gate, November, 1918
    - Two boys standing on an ancient pedestal, undated
    - Circle drive and gardens in front of building, uknown
    - Collapsed ancient ruins, undated
    - View of scenery through lattice, undated
    - People walking in courtyard, undated
    - Crowd gathered in front of building, November 1917
    - People ascending courtyard stairs, undated
    - Elaborately ornamented building faade, undated
    - Statue of a lion in courtyard, undated
    - Courtyard garden, undated
    - A group of people resting and eating, undated
    - People traveling through an arch, undated
    - Overgrown steps leading to a pagoda style building, undated
    - Woman holding parasol, standing among ancient ruins, undated
    - The Great Wall of China near Nankow Pass, undated
  - Central Field Health Station, 2 (Box 25, Folder 302)
    - Central Field Health Station Album, uknown
      - Central Field Health Station Postcard, undated
      - New building at Central Field Health Station, undated
      - Entire front of Central Hospital, uknown
      - Entrance of Central Hospital, undated
      - West side of Central Hospital, undated
      - Front entrance of Central Hospital, undated
      - Main entrance of Central Hospital, undated
      - Central Hospital driveway, undated
      - Back of Central Hospital, undated
      - View of Vaccine Room, undated
      - Scientists working in the Dissecting Room, undated
      - Scientist preparing a vitamin B for injection, undated
      - People manufacturing Ephedrine, undated
      - People catching mosquitoes, undated
      - People searching for mosquito larvae, undated
      - Man mixing Paris Green and road dust, undated
      - Kala-azar patient examination, undated
      - Baby Health Contest participants, undated
      - People posing with Health Campaign float, undated
      - Student being vaccinated with classmates waiting, undated
      - Doctors posing with mobile clinic truck, undated
      - Midwife with babies, undated
      - Two men fumigating a train, undated
      - Fumigation device attached to train
      - Group portrait of the Highway Health Teams, undated
      - Display of first-aid boxes, undated
      - Two students making anatomical models, undated
      - Three students making anatomical models, undated
      - Good posture propaganda, undated
      - Dental hygiene propaganda, undated
      - Health Propaganda - Anti-cholera parade, Shanghai
      - Health Propaganda - Health campaign, Nanking
      - Health Education - Part of Health Exhibit I
      - Health Education - Part of Health Exhibit II
      - Health Education - Part of Health Exhibit III
      - Health Education - School Health, Morning Inspection
      - Health Education - School Health, Physical Examination
      - Medical Health Work of Nanking Military Academy
        - Physical Examination
        - Physical Examination - Medical, Lungs
        - Physical Examination - E. N. T.
        - Physical Examination Hall
        - Physical Examination - Medical, Heart.
        - Disinfection of wells
        - Disinfection and cleansing of latrines
        - Collect of sample for water analysis
        - Inspection of Dining Room
        - Inspection of Kitchen
        - Suppression of flies
        - Portable Latrines for Demonstration
        - Hospital Building
        - Clinical Rounds, Medical
        - Operation Room
        - Clinical Lab
        - Medical O. P. D.
        - Surgical O. P. D.
        - Hospital Pharmacy
        - Java type latrine for field use
        - Military Medical Service, Central Military Academy,Field Service
        - ENT and Eye O. P. D.
        - Sanitary Troop, Military Medical Service, Central Military Academy
        - Military Medical Officers, Central Military Academy
        - Sanitary Troop (Stretcher Bearers)
        - Artesian Well prepared by Sanitary Troop for Spring maneuver
        - Statistical Service
        - Spring maneuver, Central Military Academy
        - First Aid Station, Military Academy, Nanking
        - Postcard of entrance to unidentified building
        - Business Office
        - Whole Staff of the Service, Nanking Military Academy
  - National Flood Relief Commission Album, circa 1932; 3 (Box 25, Folder 303)
  - Peking Union Medical College 1 - Album, 4 (Box 26, Folder 304)
  - Peking Union Medical College 1 - Album, 5 (Box 26, Folder 305)
  - Peking Union Medical College 1 - Album (Box 26, Folder 306)
  - Peking Union Medical College 1 - Album - Dedication Activities, 1921 September; 7 (Box 27, Folder 307)
  - Peking Union Medical College 1 - Album - Dedication Activities - Duplicates, 1921 September; 8 (Box 27, Folder 308)
  - Peking Union Medical College 1 - Album - Ying Compound, 1920-1921; 9 (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - Peking Union Medical College 1 - Yu Wang Fu, 1917-1918; 10 (Box 27, Folder 310)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2 - Exteriors, 1918; 1926; 1933; 11 (Box 27, Folder 311)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2 - Exteriors - Construction, 1918; 12 (Box 27, Folder 312)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2 - Exteriors - Construction, 1917-1919; 13 (Box 27, Folder 313)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2 - Exteriors - Construction, 1918-1919; 14 (Box 28, Folder 314)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2 - Exteriors -Construction, 1920; 15 (Box 28, Folder 315)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2 - Exteriors - Construction, 1920; 16 (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2 - Exteriors - Construction, 1917-1920, 1922, 1926; 17 (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2a - Exteriors - Groups, 1920-1927; 18 (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2a "R" - Exteriors - Groups - Residences, 1917-1922, 1925-1926, 1938; 19 (Box 29, Folder 319)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2b - Exteriors - Individual Buildings, 1918-1929; 20 (Box 29, Folder 320)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2b - Exteriors - Individual Buildings, 1918-1926 (Box 29, Folder 321)
  - Peking Union Medical College 2c - Exteriors - Details, 1918-1926; 21 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Peking Union Medical College 3 - Interiors, 1919-1926; 24 (Box 29, Folder 323)
  - Peking Union Medical College 3a - Interiors - Laboratories, 1919-1922; 25 (Box 30, Folder 324)
  - Peking Union Medical College 3a - Interiors - Laboratories, 1919-1929; 26 (Box 30, Folder 325)
  - Peking Union Medical College 3a - Interiors - Laboratories, undated; 27 (Box 30, Folder 326)
  - Peking Union Medical College 3b - Interiors - Libraries, 1920-1927; 28 (Box 30, Folder 327)
  - Peking Union Medical College 3c - Interiors - Wards, 1920-1926; 29 (Box 30, Folder 328)
  - Peking Union Medical College 3d - Interiors - Dispensary, 1921-1924, 1933; 30 (Box 30, Folder 329)
  - Peking Union Medical College 3f - Interiors - Others, 1921-1928; 31 (Box 30, Folder 330)
  - Peking Union Medical College 5-Animals / 11-Rolling Stock, 1920-1927 (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - People at Ceremonies, 33 (Box 30, Folder 332)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12abc - Groups - Staff/Graduates, 1918-1923; 34 (Box 31, Folder 333)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12abc - Groups - Staff/Graduates, 1921-1923; 35 (Box 31, Folder 334)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12abc - Groups - Staff/Graduates, 1921-1926; 36 (Box 31, Folder 335)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12abc - Groups - Staff/Graduates, 1921-1934, 1946; 37 (Box 31, Folder 336)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12abc - Groups - Staff/Graduates (Misc.), 1922-1950; 38 (Box 31, Folder 337)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Albrecht/Chan, 39 (Box 31, Folder 338)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Chang/Chow, 40 (Box 32, Folder 339)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Chu/Griffith, 41 (Box 32, Folder 340)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Hahn/Huang, 42 (Box 32, Folder 341)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Ingram/Li, 43 (Box 32, Folder 342)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Li/Lyman, 44 (Box 33, Folder 343)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Ma/Rothe, 45 (Box 33, Folder 344)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individual - Staff - Sah/Von Bonin, 46 (Box 33, Folder 345)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Walker/Wung, 47 (Box 33, Folder 346)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Staff - Yang/Zurovec, 48 (Box 33, Folder 347)
  - Peking Union Medical College 12 - Individuals - Students - Classes, 1934-1940; 49 (Box 33, Folder 348)
  - Peking Union Medical College 13 - Health Station, 1930, undated; 50 (Box 34, Folder 349)
  - Peking Union Medical College 14 - Cenezoic Laboratory, 1930, 1934-1937; 51 (Box 34, Folder 350)
  - Peking Union Medical College 15 - Pre-Medical School, 1919-1922, 1925; 52 (Box 34, Folder 351)
  - Peking Union Medical College 16 - City Psychopathic Hospital - Album, 53 (Box 34, Folder 352)
  - Red Cross Society of China - North China Medical Relief Commission Album, 1933; 54 (Box 34, Folder 353)
  - Sun Yat-Sen Funeral, 1925; 55 (Box 34, Folder 354)
  - Peking Union Medical College - Eva Macmillan Photographs, circa 1925; 56 (Box 35, Folder 355)
  - First Health Station Album, 1936 January 24; 57 (Box 35, Folder 356)
  - Peking Union Medical College - Exteriors
  - Peking Union Medical College - Interiors
  - Peking Union Medical College
  - China Medical Board Oversize Photographs
  - Peiping Tuberculosis Center
  - Pageant of Peking, The
  - National Public Health Activities - Nanking China